All the game "hidden" features explained: 			(By: Cody - the game mechanics dev ¯\_(ツ)_/¯)

//The list is in no specific order
//Don't mind the text emojis
// | (• ◡•)| (❍ᴥ❍ʋ)



- If you press the chicken in the main menu, it will "jump" (just try it out, i don't know how to explain it)

- Type the easter egg code in the main menu to unlock the cheat code: DOWN DOWN UP UP UP UP UP UP UP UP UP
 (down 2 times, up 9 times)
 (It's the megaman x black zero cheat code)

- You are invincable when cheat code is on

- The movement of the chicken in the first level (and the main menu) is actually random 

- The movement of the boss is "slightly random", but it'll move to a random position with the current ship position as the 
 mean value for random (sketchy explain, i know. Just go to the bossRandom part and you'll know what i mean). Use that to 
 make the game slightly easier to beat (probably)

- Eggs drop rate is random as: For every 30 to 240 frames (depends on level), the chickens have a chance to drop the
 egg (8/10, i think so)

- Damage profile of weapons:	 ▄︻̷̿┻̿═━一
  + Red gun: 1 damage
  + Green gun: 1.5 damage
  + Yellow gun: 0.5 damage
 Damage formula: (weapon type) + 0.5 * (weapon level)	
 Base health of chicken is 1, btw. Some level, it'll be higher

- If you want to play any level, just head to the beginning part (the one that list the variables), and change the 
 "levelXSetup" boolean to true (X is the level you want to try, and don't forget to change the old one back to false).
 But you won't see that "wave X......" part at the beginning of that level

- Developer option: If you're in the X level, you can press that number (i.e: you press 1 during level 1 to skip it; 
 except for level 10 you press 0), to skip that level. It's mainly used during the testing so it's not "polished", and
 it'll looks really weird. Though it may be pretty useful due to the lack of time to do the presentation 

- The coordinates of chicken in level6 is random, so it may looks a bit weird

- Good luck beating the veteran difficulty. Esp when i put tons of more eggs, double the health and lower box drop rate 
 at the same time	(ノಠ益ಠ)ノ彡┻━┻

- The green gun shoot very slow, but you can press it rapidly to make it fires faster	(•ω•)

- You can technically makes the game run faster by increase the frameRate (i still keep some of the value somewhere in the 
 setup). Though it may get seriously laggy

- 
 

